Guide to the Stanford University, Vice President for Business Affairs, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Stern - Units 7 & 8 - Construction I (Add. #2 - Completion), 1957 (Box 113, Folder 12)
- Stone, Calvin P. (Mrs.), 1935-1968 (Box 82, Folder 26)
- Stone, Evelyn H. (Mrs.), 1940-1955 (Box 82, Folder 27)
- Stone, George, 1931 (Box 82, Folder 28)
- Stores Building - Office Expansion, 802, 1973-1974 (Box 109, Folder 16)
- Stores - Chemistry, 1960-1967 (Box 60, Folder 9)
- Stores, 2, 1959-1971 (Box 60, Folder 8)
- Stores, Folder 1, 1932-1959 (Box 82, Folder 29)
- Storey House, 1928 ?-1949 (Box 82, Folder 30)
- Storke Publications, Room 103 Alterations, (911), 1974-1975 (Box 108, Folder 24)
- Stowe, Lyman M., 1958-1966 (Box 82, Folder 31)
- Strassberger, Paul (used car lot), 1952-1962 (Box 82, Folder 32)
- Strong, E. K., Jr., 1934-1958 (Box 82, Folder 33)
- Stuart, Graham, 1927-1937 (Box 82, Folder 34)
- Student Discipline - Exhibits (Box 60, Folder 11)
- Student Discipline, 1963 (Box 60, Folder 10)
- Student Publications Building - Legal Documents, 133, 1962-1964 (Box 102, Folder 24)
- Student Services Building (Old Union Remodeling) - Legal, 1965-1967 (Box 102, Folder 23)
- Subdivisions - Grounds Maintenance - Green Valley Contract, 1972-1974 (Box 89, Folder 2)
- Subordination Agreement, 1935-1937 (Box 82, Folder 35)
- Subordination Agreements - General, 1959-1972 (Box 60, Folder 12)
- Subordination Agreements - General, 1942-1959 (Box 83, Folder 6)
- Subordination Agreements, 1948-1949 (Box 82, Folder 36)
- Subordination Agreements, 1949-1950 (Box 83, Folder 1)
- Subordination Agreements, 1950-1951 (Box 83, Folder 2)
- Subordination Agreements, 1952-1953 (Box 83, Folder 3)
- Subordination Agreements, 1954-1955 (Box 83, Folder 4)
- Subordination Agreements, 1955-1956 (Box 83, Folder 5)
- Subway - Highway 101 and Univ. Ave., 1937-1941 (Box 83, Folder 7)
- Subway - S.P. Tracks and Univ. Ave., 1937-1939 (Box 83, Folder 8)
- Summary of Proposed Letter Agreement with Urban Coalition, 1960-1970 (Box 89, Folder 4)
- Suppes, Patrick, 680 Foothill Rd., 1952-1961 (Box 83, Folder 9)
- Sutliffe, Helen Binninger, 1950-1951 (Box 83, Folder 10)
- Swain, R. E., 1933 (Box 83, Folder 11)
- Swain, Robert E., 1938-1963 (Box 83, Folder 12)
- Swank, Raynard C., 1949-1962 (Box 83, Folder 13)
- Swerling, Boris C., 1958-1962 (Box 83, Folder 14)
- Syntex Animal Research - Exhibits (Box 83, Folder 18)
- Syntex Laboratories, Inc. (Animal Research Center) - Correspondence I, 1967-1968 (Box 83, Folder 15)
- Syntex Laboratories, Inc. (Animal Research Center) - Correspondence II, 1968-1969 (Box 83, Folder 16)
- Syntex Laboratories, Inc. (Animal Research Center) - Correspondence III, 1969-1970 (Box 83, Folder 17)
- Taggart, Thomas N., 1963-1964 (Box 83, Folder 20)
- Tamarit, Schooner (Donald A McCormick), Charter by S.E.L., 1962 (Box 83, Folder 19)
- Tatum, June A., 1948-1968 (Box 83, Folder 21)
- Tax & Assessment Service (Cal Tax Agency), 1951-1956 (Box 85, Folder 22)
- Tax Assessment Map Numbers, 1957 (Box 71, Folder 22)
- Tax Assessments - Comparisons, 1936-1939 (Box 85, Folder 10)
- Tax Assessments, 1943-1944 (Box 85, Folder 3)
- Tax Assessments, 1944-1945 (Box 85, Folder 4)
- Tax Assessments, 1945-1946 (Box 85, Folder 5)
- Tax Assessments, 1946-1947 (Box 85, Folder 6)
- Tax Assessments, 1947-1948 (Box 85, Folder 7)
- Tax Assessments, 1948-1949 (Box 85, Folder 8)
- Tax Assessments, 1949-1950 (Box 85, Folder 9)
- Tax Assessments, 1950-1954 (Binder) (Box 83)
- Tax Assessments, 1924-1949 (Box 85, Folder 2)
- Tax Exemptions - Correspondence Procedures and Claims, 1953-1960 (Box 85, Folder 21)
- Tax Exemptions - General, 1921-1965 (Box 85, Folder 11)
- Tax Exemptions, 1941 (Box 85, Folder 12)
- Tax Exemptions, 1943-1944 (Box 85, Folder 13)
- Tax Exemptions, 1944-1945 (Box 85, Folder 14)
- Tax Exemptions, 1945-1946 (Box 85, Folder 15)
- Tax Exemptions, 1946-1947 (Box 85, Folder 16)
- Tax Exemptions, 1948-1949 (Box 85, Folder 17)
- Tax Exemptions, 1949-1950 (Box 85, Folder 18)
- Tax Exemptions, 1950-1952 (Box 85, Folder 19)
- Tax Exemptions, 1952-1953 (Box 85, Folder 20)
- Tax Information - Construction, 1953-1954 (Box 85, Folder 23)
- Tax Information - Land Development, 1954-1955 (Box 85, Folder 24)
- Taxation, 1932-1941 (Box 85, Folder 25)
- Taxes - Alameda County, 1955-1957 (Box 84, Folder 7)
- Taxes - Annual Tax Exemption Affadavit, 1960-1966 (Box 84, Folder 2)
- Taxes - Annual Tax Exemption Affadavit, 1966-1969 (Box 84, Folder 3)
- Taxes - Annual Tax Exemption Affadavit, 1969-1971 (Box 84, Folder 4)
- Taxes - Annual Tax Exemption Affadavit, 1971-1972 (Box 84, Folder 8)
- Taxes - Annual Tax Exemption Affidavit, 1972-1973 (Box 60, Folder 14)
- Taxes - Annual Tax Exemption Affidavit, 1973-1974 (Box 60, Folder 13)
- Taxes - Assessment Formulas, 1951-1955 (Box 84, Folder 6)
- Taxes - Building Coverage Report, 1955 (Box 60, Folder 15)
- Taxes - City of Palo Alto, 1954-1965 (Box 84, Folder 5)
- Taxes - Educational Exemption; Assembly Bills #1, 1951-1961 (Box 84, Folder 1)
- Taxes - Frenchman’s Terrace, 1971-1973 (Box 95, Folder 26)
- Taxes - General, 1942-1965 (Box 84, Folder 9)
- Taxes - Map - Campus Property (Box 60, Folder 16)
- Taxes - Map - Monterey County (Box 60, Folder 17)
- Taxes - Map - Santa Clara County (Box 60, Folder 18)
- Taxes - Maps, Exhibits - Palo Alto, Santa Clara Co. (Box 60, Folder 21)
- Taxes - Miscellaneous #1, 1953-1971 (Box 84, Folder 10)
- Taxes - Preliminary Assessment Maps - Industrial Park Area, 1954 (Box 60, Folder 19)
- Taxes - Preliminary Assessment Maps - Shopping Center, 1954 (Box 60, Folder 20)
- Taxes - San Mateo County, 1954-1965 (Box 84, Folder 11)
- Taxes - Santa Clara County, 1952-1960 (Box 84, Folder 13)
- Taxes - Santa Clara County, 1960-1965 (Box 84, Folder 14)
- Taxes - Santa Clara County, 1965-1968 (Box 84, Folder 15)
- Taxes - Stanford Shopping Center, 1955-1965 (Box 84, Folder 12)
- Taxes - Unsecured Property #1, 1969-1972 (Box 85, Folder 1)
- Taylor, A. E., 1946-1947 (Box 85, Folder 26)
- Taylor, C. V., 1932-1948 (Box 86, Folder 1)
- Taylor, Donald W. & Ruth S., 1946-1957 (Box 86, Folder 2)
- Taylor, Elizabeth Brand, 1943-1950 (Box 86, Folder 3)
- Taylor, Frank J., 1933-1935 (Box 86, Folder 4)
- Taylor, Jos. D., 1931-1942 (Box 86, Folder 5)
- Taylor, Joseph D., 1942-1966 (Box 86, Folder 6)
- Taylor, Mrs. Minnette P. - proposed gift deed, 1937-1939 (Box 86, Folder 7)
- Te Vega - Contract Document for Repairs with Triple A Machine Shop, 1965-1966 (Box 87, Folder 8)
- Te Vega - Contract with Bethlehem Steel Corporation for Drydocking, 1965 (Box 87, Folder 7)
- Te Vega - Conversion, Folder II, 1963 (Box 87, Folder 5)
- Te Vega - Exhibits, 1965-1966 (Box 63, Folder 13)
- Te Vega - Folder #2, Yacht #1157, 1963-1964 (Box 63, Folder 12)
- Te Vega - Folder I, Conversion, 1962 (Box 87, Folder 3)
- Te Vega - Yacht 1157, Folder VI, 1967-1971 (Box 87, Folder 4)
- Te Vega Conversion - Construction, Folder #III, 1963-1966 (Box 87, Folder 6)
- Technology Licensing - Agreements, Asignments and Misc. Documents, 1971-1977 (Box 60, Folder 22)
- Technology Licensing - Yamaha FM, Sound License, 1974-1975 (Box 61, Folder 1)
- Technology Licensing #4, 1971-1973 (Box 86, Folder 8)
- Tehama County Property - SOLD, Leland Stanford’s Vina Ranch, 1927-1958 (Box 86, Folder 9)
- Teichroew, Daniel, 1961-1964 (Box 86, Folder 10)
- Telephones 1, 1945-1962 (Box 86, Folder 13)
- Telephones 2, 1960-1964 (Box 86, Folder 12)
- Telephones, For Contruction of Bldg. see "PBX - Constr.", 1953-1960 (Box 86, Folder 11)
- Television - Educational Station - Folder 1, 1967-1968 (Box 86, Folder 14)
- Television - Educational Station - Folder 2, 1968-1970 (Box 86, Folder 15)
- Terman, Dr. Lewis M., 1938-1957 (Box 87, Folder 1)
- Terman, F. E. - 659 Salvatierra, 1937-1966 (Box 87, Folder 2)
- The Balfour Building, 1939-1962 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- The Pioneer (Yacht), 1957-1965 (Box 44, Folder 5)
- Theta Chi, 1934-1940 (Box 87, Folder 9)
- Theta Chi, 1937-1953 (Box 87, Folder 10)
- Theta Delta Chi, 1947-1962 (Box 87, Folder 11)
- Theta Xi, 1935-1956 (Box 87, Folder 12)
- Thomas, David Vernon, 1961-1968 (Box 87, Folder 14)
- Thomas, Mrs. M. M., 1936 (Box 87, Folder 13)
- Thurman, Samuel D. Jr., 1958-1966 (Box 87, Folder 15)
- Tolman, D. F., 1933-1944 (Box 87, Folder 16)
- Torrance County (Property left to Stanford by Ellen F. Brown), 1957-1958 (Box 87, Folder 17)
- Total Energy - Stanford Data, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 41)
- Tower House, 1970-1971 (Box 61, Folder 2)
- Toyon Hall, 1947-1948 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Traffic and Transportation Committee Palo Alto Chamber of Commerce, 1962-1975 (Box 87, Folder 18)
- Traffic Reports - Miscellaneous Reports, Exhibits (Box 93, Folder 14)
- Traffic Studies - Miscellaneous Reports, 1954-1967 (Box 61, Folder 3)
- Traffic Studies #1, 1953-1962 (Box 87, Folder 19)
- Trails - Riding, Hiking, etc. (1), 1933-1963 (Box 87, Folder 20)
- Travel - Study of University Practices, 1962-1973 (Box 61, Folder 4)
- Travis, Martin B. (Box 87, Folder 21)
- Tresidder Bank Expansion, 973, 1975-1977 (Box 105, Folder 39)
- Tresidder Cafeteria Interim Remodeling, (920), 1974-1975 (Box 108, Folder 23)
- Tresidder Dining Alcove Renovation, 974, 1975-1977 (Box 106, Folder 1)
- Tresidder Memorial Union - General 2, 1961-1962 (Box 87, Folder 23)
- Tresidder Memorial Union - General 3, 1962-1971 (Box 87, Folder 22)
- Tresidder Memorial Union - General 1, 1948-1960 (Box 88, Folder 1)
- Tresidder Memorial Union - Indenture, 1962-1971 (Box 61, Folder 6)
- Tresidder Memorial Union - Landscaping - Construction, 1961-1963 (Box 88, Folder 2)
- Tresidder Memorial Union - Loan Agreement, 1961-1973 (Box 61, Folder 5)
- Tresidder Memorial Union - Loan Application, 1958-1961 (Box 61, Folder 7)
- Tresidder Memorial Union - Stanford Jazz, 1965-1966 (Box 61, Folder 8)
- Tresidder Union - Bowling Alley Office, 845, 1973-1975 (Box 103, Folder 28)
- Tresidder Union - Marcel’s Relocation, 969, 1975-1977 (Box 106, Folder 37)
- Tresidder Union - Store Alteration, 851, 1973-1974 (Box 103, Folder 29)
- Tresidder Union ASSU Renovations, (905), 1974-1975 (Box 108, Folder 26)
- Tresidder Union, 1971-1975 (Box 99, Folder 28)
- Troxell, John P., 1947-1966 (Box 88, Folder 3)
- Tuition - Remission of, 1939-1966 (Box 61, Folder 10)
- Tuition, 1958-1971 (Box 61, Folder 9)
- Turnover Costs (Demo Costs), 1977 (Box 33, Folder 22)
- Twitty, Victor C., 1938-1958 (Box 88, Folder 4)
- Tyson, Royal H., 1961-1968 (Box 88, Folder 5)
- U.S. Army - Air Materiel Command - Air ROTC Unit, 1946-1947 (Box 88, Folder 14)
- U.S. Fish and Wildlife Service - Transfer of Goods - Micro. Rental, 1947-1954 (Box 88, Folder 16)
- Undergraduate Financial Aid, 1972-1975 (Box 100, Folder 7)
- Undergraduate Housing #2 - Conatruction, Agreements, Board Actions, 1962-1963 (Box 103, Folder 3)
- Undergraduate Housing, First Group - Construction, Agreements, B/T Actions, 1961-1962 (Box 103, Folder 2)
- Undergraduate Men's Housing - Fraternity - Background - Programming, 1955-1958 (Box 88, Folder 9)
- Undergraduate Men's Housing - Fraternity - Fund Raising, 1956-1967 (Box 88, Folder 13)
- Undergraduate Men's Housing - Fraternity - Kitchen Consultants, 1957-1962 (Box 88, Folder 8)
- Undergraduate Men's Housing - Fraternity - Operating Agreement Negotiations, 1963-1965 (Box 88, Folder 10)
- Undergraduate Men's Housing - Fraternity - Operation and Management - Programming and Budgeting, 1957-1962 (Box 88, Folder 12)
- Undergraduate Men's Housing - Fraternity - Planning with Fraternity Representatives, 1959-1967 (Box 88, Folder 11)
- Undergraduate Men's Housing - Fraternity - Preliminary Correspondence, 1959-1962 (Box 88, Folder 6)
- Undergraduate Men's Housing - Fraternity - Warneke Cost Study, 1960 (Box 88, Folder 7)
- Union Oil Company - Specifications, Exhibits, 527 Willow Rd., 1956 (Box 61, Folder 13)
- United States - Fish and Wildlife Service - Jordan Hall - Doc. 244, 1947-1965 (Box 88, Folder 15)
- United States - Health, Education & Welfare, Dept. of, Grants under the HEF Act - Exhibits, 1965-1967 (Box 61, Folder 15)
- United States - Health, Education & Welfare, Dept. of, Grants under the Higher Educ. Facilities Act, 1963-1974 (Box 61, Folder 18)
- United States - Housing and Urban Development, Department of (formerly HHFA) - Loans under Housing Act - Background, 1950-1957 (Box 88, Folder 17)
- United States - Housing and Urban Development, Dept. of (formerly HHFA), Loans under the Housing Act of 1950, 1960-1971 (Box 61, Folder 16)
- United States - Interior, Dept. of the, Bureau of Commercial Fisheries, 1962-1970 (Box 61, Folder 19)
- United States Geological Survey, 1958-1971 (Box 61, Folder 11)
- United States Navy - Resident Representative, Office of Naval Research, 1965-1969 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- United States Post Office (campus) - Maps, 1951-1959 (Box 61, Folder 20)
- United States Post Office (on campus), 1960-1976 (Box 61, Folder 12)
- United States Post Office, 1945-1960 (Box 88, Folder 18)
- University Club - San Francisco #226, 1970-1971 (Box 61, Folder 21)
- University Laundry, 1971-1974 (Box 33, Folder 49)
- USE - Strike, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 22)
- USE Relocation, 863, 1974 (Box 103, Folder 31)
- Utilities - Storm Drain, Sewer, Water Dist. PO# 349, 350, 351, 1962-1963 (Box 88, Folder 19)
- Uzuwa, Hirofuma, 1961-1964 (Box 88, Folder 20)
- Van Epern, 1927-1949 (Box 88, Folder 24)
- Van Niel, C. B., 1947-1950 (Box 88, Folder 25)
- Van Rysselberghe, P. J., 1939-1946 (Box 88, Folder 26)
- Vander Poel Proposal - See BILLINGS, 1943 (Box 88, Folder 23)
- Vander Poel, Blanche B., 1950-1951 (Box 88, Folder 22)
- Vander Poel, Mrs. Blanche Billings, 1942-1948 (Box 88, Folder 21)
- Varian Associates - Sublease with Air Force - Corres., 1952-1957 (Box 88, Folder 27)
- Varian Basement Expansion - Legal, 480, 1966-1967 (Box 102, Folder 16)
- Varian Bldg. Helium Storage Facility, (927), 1974-1975 (Box 108, Folder 21)
- Varian Physics 002, 695, 1972-1973 (Box 109, Folder 24)
- Varsity Cleaners, 1951-1967 (Box 88, Folder 28)
- Ventura County - Property Acquired by Deed of Gift from Mr. and Mrs. John P. Thille - Sold 5-30-63, 1963-1964 (Box 88, Folder 29)
- Verba, Sidney, 1964-1968 (Box 89, Folder 7)
- Vernier, Hazel A., 1935-1962 (Box 89, Folder 8)
- Veteran's Administration Hospital (Temporary File), 1973 (Box 61, Folder 17)
- Veteran's Hospital - Correspondence, 1954-1969 (Box 89, Folder 9)
- Veteran's Hospital - Surveys, 1955 (Box 89, Folder 10)
- Vina - Water - Grover Lewis’ Diversion, 1913-1939 (Box 89, Folder 12)
- Vina Property - 1923-1931 (Box 89, Folder 21)
- Vina Property - General, 1924-1936 (Box 89, Folder 22)
- Vina Property - M. J. Jeffress, 1932 (Box 89, Folder 24)
- Vina Property Exchange, 1930-1931 (Box 89, Folder 23)
- Vina Property, 1924-1929 (Box 89, Folder 11)
- Vina Ranch - Maps - Butte and Tehama Counties, 1908-1919 (Box 89, Folder 25)
- Vina Ranch - R. W. Hanna, 1933-1935 (Box 89, Folder 19)
- Vina Ranch - Stanford Vina Irrigation District, 1922-1939 (Box 89, Folder 14)
- Vina Ranch - Stimmel, 1932-1934 (Box 89, Folder 20)
- Vina Ranch - Water Rights - Heiser Crusades Prospectors & Hoar & Garner - Law Suits, 1932-1933 (Box 89, Folder 13)
- Vina Ranch Irrigation Co. (?), 1923-1924 (Box 89, Folder 15)
- Vina Ranch Property, 1923 (Box 89, Folder 16)
- Vina Ranch Property, 1925-1927 (Box 89, Folder 18)
- Vina Ranch Property,1927-1928 (Box 89, Folder 17)
- Volkart, Edmund H., 1955-1962 (Box 90, Folder 22)
- Volkart, Edmund H., 1962 (Box 90, Folder 21)
- Vucinich, Wayne S., 1947-1948 (Box 90, Folder 23)
- W, 1956-1965 (Box 90, Folder 24)
- Wages - Women's Residences & Dining Halls, 1942-1953 (Box 90, Folder 25)
- Wagner and Martinez, 1940-1953 (Box 90, Folder 27)
- Wagner, Harvey M., 1962-1967 (Box 90, Folder 26)
- Walt, Frank Motors (used car lot), 1955-1958 (Box 90, Folder 28)
- Washington, Univ. of - Information re Construction, Physical Plant & Residences, 1963-1967 (Box 90, Folder 29)
- Water - Exhibits, Reports, maps, etc., I, 1957-1963 (Box 91, Folder 6)
- Water - Exhibits, Reports, maps, etc., II, 1949-1963 (Box 91, Folder 7)
- Water - Flood Control - General, Also see: San Francisquito Creek, 1962-1974 (Box 61, Folder 24)
- Water - Maps, misc., III, 1957-1963 (Box 91, Folder 8)
- Water - Wells, Folder I, 1941-1949 (Box 100, Folder 12)
- Water - Wells, Folder II, 1950-1965 (Box 61, Folder 23)
- Water 3 (Contains Kennedy and Bradberry Correspondence), 1960 (Box 91, Folder 1)
- Water 4 (see also: Water - San Francisco Water Co.), 1961 (Box 91, Folder 2)
- Water 5 (see also: Water - San Francisco Water Co., San Francisquito Creek - Flood Control, Water - Wells, Lake Lagunita, Searsville Lake), 1961-1962 (Box 91, Folder 3)
- Water 6, 1962-1964 (Box 91, Folder 4)
- Water 7, 1965-1967 (Box 91, Folder 5)
- Water Report - Carroll E. Bradberry, Preliminary, Folder I, 1960 (Box 100, Folder 8)
- Water Report - Carroll E. Bradberry, Preliminary, Folder II, 1960 (Box 100, Folder 9)
- Water Rights - Los Trancos Creek, 1931-1945 (Box 61, Folder 25)
- Water Supply Survey, 1959-1962 (Box 100, Folder 11)
- Water Supply, 1961-1962 (Box 61, Folder 26)
- Water Systems Distribution - G. P. I., 1965-1967 (Box 101, Folder 32)
- Water, 1947-1954 (Box 90, Folder 31)
- Water, 1954-1958 (Box 90, Folder 32)
- Water, 1959-1959 for “Flood Control” see San Francisquito Cr. (Box 90, Folder 33)
- Water, 1900-1947 (Box 90, Folder 30)
- Watkins Flowerland - Watkins, Robert L., 1954-1963 (Box 100, Folder 13)
- Webb, George, 1939-1951 (Box 100, Folder 14)
- Webster, D.L. & Anna C., 1951-1960 (Box 100, Folder 15)
- Webster, Prof. Hutton, 1931-1933 (Box 100, Folder 16)
- Weed Abatement, 1950-1964 (Box 100, Folder 17)
- Weiss Property - Berkeley, 1931-1955 (Box 100, Folder 19)
- Weiss Property - Palo Alto, 1953-1957 (Box 100, Folder 18)
- Wells Fargo Bank - Tresidder Union Branch, Exhibits B and C to lease August 1, 1972 (Box 61, Folder 27)
- Wells Fargo Bank and Union Trust Co., 1940-1972 (Box 62, Folder 1)
- Weltner, C. B., 1958-1965 (Box 100, Folder 20)
- Wert, Robert J., 1959-1967 (Box 100, Folder 21)
- West Side Circulation Phase I, 433G, 402G, 475A - Legal & Disbursements, 1966-1967 (Box 103, Folder 7)
- Whitaker and Baxter (2), 1960-1961 (Box 101, Folder 1)
- Whitaker and Baxter, 1960 (Box 100, Folder 22)
- Whitaker, A. C., 1950-1964 (Box 101, Folder 2)
- Whitaker, Virgil K., 1949-1956 (Box 101, Folder 3)
- White Memorial Plaza - Legal Documents, 1963-1964 (Box 102, Folder 17)
- White, Charles Langdon, 1943-1965 (Box 101, Folder 4)
- White, Lynn T., Jr., 1942-1944 (Box 101, Folder 5)
- Wilbur Hall - Junipero Lounge Fire, 1973-1975 (Box 108, Folder 18)
- Wilbur Hall, Otero Food Service Dorm Rehab., File I, 836, 1973-1974 (Box 103, Folder 19)
- Wilbur Property, 1945-1953 (Box 101, Folder 6)
- Willey, George A., 1957-1964 (Box 101, Folder 7)
- Williams Property (Thomas & Dora Williams), 1944-1958 (Box 101, Folder 8)
- Williams Property (Thomas & Dora Williams), 1958-1962 (Box 101, Folder 9)
- Williams, C. H., P. A. Farm, 1950-1956 (Box 101, Folder 10)
- Williams, Harry A., 1955-1966 (Box 101, Folder 11)
- Williams, Joseph E., 616 Foothill Road, 1950-1961 (Box 101, Folder 12)
- Willis, Bailey, 1933-1950 (Box 101, Folder 13)
- Willow Creek Apartments - Pacific Planners Proposal, 1958-1961 (Box 101, Folder 14)
- Willow Road Assessment, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 27)
- Willow Road Improvements - Pasteur to Bridge - Utilities, 1959-1960 (Box 101, Folder 15)
- Winder, Clarence L., 1950-1961 (Box 101, Folder 16)
- Winter, Merch, 1938-1949 (Box 101, Folder 17)
- Wise, Harold F. & Associates - Correspondence, 1955 (Box 101, Folder 18)
- Wise, Harold F. & Associates - Reports, 1955 (Box 101, Folder 19)
- Wolters, Maria, 1941-1942 (Box 101, Folder 20)
- Women’s Gym - Men’s Shower Alteration, 656, 1971-1972 (Box 104, Folder 5)
- Woodside - Proposed Incorporation, 1953-1958 (Box 101, Folder 21)
- Work, James, 1949-1951 (Box 101, Folder 22)
- Xerox - Coyote Hill, 1970-1973 (Box 98, Folder 2)
- Xerox - General, 1965-1969 (Box 62, Folder 2)
- Yost, Mary, 1935-1961 (Box 101, Folder 23)
- Zoning - Educational, 1958-1965 (Box 62, Folder 4)
- Zoning - Palo Alto, C. Davis Office Development, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 6)
- Zoning - Palo Alto, Deer Gulch Golf Course, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 5)
- Zoning - Portola Valley, 1965-1971 (Box 62, Folder 7)
- Zoning - Woodside, 1958-1967 (Box 62, Folder 9)
- Zoning- Portola Valley, Exhibits, 1964-1967 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- Zoning, 1950-1976 (Box 62, Folder 3)